TeleLearning Network Inc. fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Research files, 1995 - 2002; F-172-6; 30 cm of textual records 17.2 mb. of textual records (electronic)
  - Research theme and project reports, 1995 - 2001; F-172-6-2; 4 cm of textual records 16.9 mb. of textual records (electronic)
    Sub-series consists of records submitted by TeleLearning Theme and Project Leaders in compliance with Network reporting requirements. The records comprise reports on theme and project progress and results. Record media include paper and electronic; electronic records are retained in their original software format (.doc).
    Files are arranged by type of report, and within these groupings chronologically by year.
    - Research project overviews, 1996 - 1997; F-172-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Theme reports, 1996; F-172-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Theme reports, 1997; F-172-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Theme reports, 1999; F-172-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 172-20)
    - Progress reports '95-'96, 1995 - 1996; F-172-6-2-0-5
    - Progress reports '97, 1997; F-172-6-2-0-6
    - Progress reports '98, 1999; F-172-6-2-0-7
    - Progress reports '00, 2000; F-172-6-2-0-8
    - Progress reports '01, 2001; F-172-6-2-0-9
    - Project reports '97, 1997; F-172-6-2-0-10
    - Project reports '99, 1999; F-172-6-2-0-11
  - Project management files, 1995 - 2002; F-172-6-3; 17 cm of textual records 0.32 mb. of textual records (electronic)
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the administration of certain TeleLearning projects by the Network's management office. Projects include the Portal for Online Objects in Learning (POOL); a TeleLearning legacy book and a research handbook and two initiatives funded by the Office of Learning Technologies (Human Resources Development Canada) -- "Training and mentoring of instructors and course authors for TeleLearning using Virutal-U" and "A framework of policy studies for telelearning technologies."
    Records include proposals, contracts, agreements and memoranda of understanding, correspondence, reports, specifications, notes and working papers, budgets, spreadsheets, invoices, claim forms and supporting documentation. Record media include paper and electronic; electronic records are retained in their original software format (.doc).
    Files are organized by project title.
    File list is available.
    - Office of Learning Technology project - A framework for policy studies of telelearning technologies, 1996 - 1997; F-172-6-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-21)
    - Office of Learning Technology project -Training and mentoring of instructors and course authors for TeleLearning using Virtual-U, 1995 - 1998; F-172-6-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-21)
    - Portal for Online Objects in Learning (POOL), vol. 1, 2000 - 2002; F-172-6-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 172-21)
    - Portal for Online Objects in Learning (POOL), vol. 2, 2000 - 2002; F-172-6-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 172-21)
    - Portal for Online Objects in Learning (POOL), vol. 3, 2000 - 2002; F-172-6-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 172-21)
    - Portal for Online Objects in Learning (POOL), vol. 4, 2000 - 2002; F-172-6-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 172-21)
    - TeleLearning Innovation in Canada - legacy book, 2002; F-172-6-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 172-22)
    - Understanding ELearning - TeleLearning research handbook, 2002; F-172-6-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 172-22)
    - Office of Learning Technology project - Training and mentoring of instructors and course authors for TeleLearning using Virtual-U, vol. 2, 1995 - 1998; F-172-6-3-0-9
    - Project Revamp, 1997; F-172-6-3-0-10
- Spin-off companies files, 1998 - 2002; F-172-7; 21 cm of textual records 7.7 mb. of textual records (electronic)
  This series consists of records relating to TeleLearning spin-off companies, including InVentures Incubator Inc., TeleLearning Solutions Inc., CLEARMed Inc., TELEStraining Inc., ThoughtShare Communications Inc., and Virtual Learning Environments Inc. Activities documented include company establishment, business and strategic planning, promotion, and the Network's purchase and / or sale of company shares.
  Records include proposals, correspondence, reports, agreements, contracts and memoranda of understanding, meeting minutes, business plans, certificates of incorporation (copies), company by-laws, project files, work plans, promotional material, media releases, financial statements, invoices, share agreements and certificates. Record media include paper and electronic; electronic records are retained in their original software formats (.doc, .rtf, .ppt, .xls, and .pdf).
  See also sub-series F-172-1-1, "Board of Directors meeting records" for more information relating to TeleLearning spin-off companies.
  - InVentures Incubator Inc., vol. 1, 2000 - 2002; F-172-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 172-22)
  - InVentures Incubator Inc., vol. 2, 2000 - 2002; F-172-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 172-22)
  - InVentures Incubator Inc., vol. 3, 2000 - 2002; F-172-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 172-22)
  - InVentures Incubator Inc., vol. 4, 2000 - 2002; F-172-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 172-22)
  - InVentures Incubator Inc. - Executive Director, 2000; F-172-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 172-23)
  - Spin-off companies, 2001; F-172-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 172-23)
  - Tech transfer - CEO's file, 1998 - 1999; F-172-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 172-23)
  - TeleLearning Solutions Inc., vol. 1, 2002; F-172-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 172-23)
  - TeleLearning Solutions Inc. - Belize project, 2001; F-172-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 172-23)
  - TELEStraining Inc, vol. 1, 2000; F-172-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 172-23)
  - CLEARMed Inc., 1999 - 2000; F-172-7-0-0-11
  - InVentures Incubator Inc., vol. 5, 2000 - 2002; F-172-7-0-0-12
  - TELEStraining Inc., vol. 2, 1999 - 2000; F-172-7-0-0-13
  - ThoughtShare Communications Inc., 1999; F-172-7-0-0-14
  - TeleLearning Solutions Inc., vol. 2, 2000 - 2002; F-172-7-0-0-15
  - Virtual Learning Environments Inc., 1999; F-172-7-0-0-16